

Ionuț-Claudiu Leonte

Date of birth: 19/06/1998

Nationality: Romanian

#### CONTACT



leonteionut98@yahoo.com



(+40) 0727304987



https://leonteportfolio.netlify.app/



#### **ABOUT ME**

In the past: I worked at CLdN Malta Ltd as an Engine Cadet with an international team.

Now: I am a student at the IT School in the "Front-end Web Development" course. Future goal: I look forward to working as a Front-end Web Developer.

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

07/2022 - CURRENT

## Front-end Web Developer

IT School

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, React.js, Git

*In progress to obtain the front-end web developer certification.* 

Field of study Computer Software Engineering

**2017 - 2021** - Constanța, Romania

### Constanta Maritime University

Faculty of Naval Electromechanics

**Address** Constanța, Romania | **Field of study** Engineering | **Final grade** 9.

**2013 - 2017** - Brăila, Romania

### High school graduation

"Nicolae Bălcescu" National College, Brăila

**Address** Brăila, Romania | **Field of study** Mathematics - Informatics (informatics intensive) | **Final grade** 8.38

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2021 - 2022

# Engine Cadet - Ro/Ro Ships

CLdN Malta Ltd.

- ∘ Had 3 trips contracts in 2021-2022 year.
- Assisting with any planned maintenance work.
- Helping to operate pump and fuel systems, distribution and electrical generating equipment, air conditioning plants, refrigeration systems, and cranes and lifts.
- $\,^\circ\,$  Stripping engines and inspecting their components.
- Tracing out (following) the paths of oil, water or steam as they travel through the ship's systems.
- Taking note of daily logs from the equipment in the engine room.
- Taking soundings (measuring how much fluid is in a tank.)
- Helping to keep watch in the engine room.
- Cleaning, painting and greasing equipment

05/2019 - 03/2020 - Constanța, Romania

Delivery driver

SC HELLOHUNGRY SA

#### **DIGITAL SKILLS**

# **My Digital Skills**

Microsoft Office - advanced level / HTML / Github / CSS / JavaScript & jQuery junior knowledge / React.js

# COMMUNICATION AND INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Communication

Teamwork

Flexible Schedule

**Easily Adaptable** 

**Active-learning** 

#### LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Romanian

**OTHER LANGUAGE(S):** 

**English** 

Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	Writing
C2	C2	C2	C2	C2

#### German

<b>Listening</b>	<b>Reading</b>	<b>Spoken production</b> B2	Spoken interaction	Writing
B2	B2		B2	B2
DZ	DZ	DZ.	BZ	DZ

# **HOBBIES**

Travelling , Sports , Cars , Music , Movies , Video Gaming

## **DRIVING LICENCE**

Driving Licence: AM
Driving Licence: B1
Driving Licence: B

# **PASSPORT**

Yes

## **SEAMAN'S BOOK**

Yes

• Registration number: 38860CT

#### **CERTIFICATES**

Basic Training (IMO)

1.Personal survival techniques

2.Personal safety and social responsabilities on board ships

3.Basic fire-fighting

4.Elementary first aid

o Certificate No.: 00026829

# **Certificate of Proficiency**

° Certificate of Proficiency No. : 85208

Security awareness training & security training for seafarers with designated security duties (IMO)

° Certificate No.: 00007621

Certificate of Proficiency in Welding Technologies and Equipment

Certificate of Proficiency to perform functions, on board oil tankers and chemical tankers

Certificate of working in Confined Space